<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="test_stylesheet.xsl"?>
<!--I was messing with a stylesheet since i did an xlink and wanted to see if the link worked, unfrotunately i am too tired to figure it out fully-->
<root xmlns:xlink="https://www.loc.gov/item/44028152/">
    <heading num="1">Shrewsbury Cakes: Original Recipe.</heading>
    <para num="one">
        <info>This recipe comes from MS Codex 625, a manuscript recipe book that belonged to a
            student in a <place>London</place> cooking school in the early eighteenth century. The
            pastry school was owned by <person type="headmaster">Edward Kidder</person>, who taught
            at a few locations in <place>London</place> between around <year>1720 and 1734</year>.
            Blank books with printed title pages seem to have been used by students to write down
            recipes they learned. <person type="headmaster">Kidder</person> also published his
            recipes in the printed volume, <kidder xlink:type="simple"
                xlink:href="https://www.loc.gov/item/44028152/">Receipts for Pastry and
                Cookery</kidder>, in <year>1720</year>.</info>
    </para>
    <original>
        <para num="two">Take a <measurment>pound</measurment> of fresh butter a pound of double
            refind sugar sifted fine a little beaten mace &amp; 4 eggs beat them all together with.
            your hands till tis very leight &amp; looks curdling you put thereto a pound &amp; 1/2
            of <plant>flower</plant> roul them out into little cakes</para>
        <!--Four eggs seems like a lot, even for a recipe this old-->
        <!--Then again, a pound of butter and sugar seems like a lot too, but really isnt-->
    </original>
    <new>
        <heading num="2"> Our recipe (halved from the original)</heading>
        <para num="three">

            <dry>
                <ingredient>
                    <measurment type="pound">1/2 lb.</measurment> sugar</ingredient>
                <ingredient>
                    <measurment type="teaspoon">1/4 tsp.</measurment> mace</ingredient>
                <ingredient>
                    <measurment type="teaspoon">1/2 tsp.</measurment> cinnamon</ingredient>
                <ingredient>
                    <measurment type="pound">3/4 lb.</measurment> flour</ingredient>
                <!--Please dont use hamsters when baking, thank you-->
            </dry>
            <wet>
                <ingredient>2 eggs</ingredient>
                <ingredient>
                    <measurment type="pound">1/2 lb.</measurment> (2 sticks) butter,
                    softened</ingredient>
            </wet>

        </para>
        <steps>
            <para num="four">Using an <tool>electric mixer</tool>, cream together the butter and
                sugar. Then add the eggs and mix at medium speed until the mixture looks curdled.
                    <tool>Sift</tool> together dry ingredients and add at low speed until just
                combined. <tool>Scoop</tool> and roll the dough by hand into 1-tbsp. balls, then pat
                flat. [You could also refrigerate the dough until it’s firm enough to roll out on a
                flat surface and cut out into rounds.]</para>
            <para num="five">Bake at <temp>350F</temp> for <time>15-18 minutes</time> (ours were
                about <measurment>1/3″</measurment> thick, so you could roll them thinner and have a
                slightly shorter cooking time). They’re done once they turn the slightest bit brown
                around the edges. This halved recipe yielded about two dozen cookies.</para>
        </steps>
        <heading num="3">The Results</heading>
        <para num="six">If you like <food>snickerdoodles</food> (and who doesn’t?), you’d like
            these. We added the cinnamon because we like it and couldn’t resist, and we thought it
            rounded out the mace nicely. These are mild, fairly soft cookies that are great with
            tea. We rolled and patted the dough into individual cookies because it was too soft and
            stick to roll out, but a little bit more flour and a stint in the fridge might make the
            dough easier to work with a <tool>rolling pin</tool>.</para>
    </new>
</root>
